mybaseguide.com 2019-10-30

# MyBaseGuide - Military Relocation Services and Information - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the online information collection practices of MARCOA Media, LLC and MyBaseGuide brand products, including MyBaseGuide.com and our related services, as a part of JumpCrew, LLC (“we”, “us”, “our”, or “ours”).

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may provide to use or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).  In addition, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any activities (online or otherwise) of our printed publications.  

 **CONSENT** : by visiting and continuing to use this website, you are accepting the practices and policies described below and you consent to being bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.  _If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site._   

* **Location of Processing**

We operate in the United States.  Our servers and offices are located in the United States and therefore personal data about you may be transferred to, stored, or processed in the United States.

* **Duration of Processing**

We limit our retention of your personal data to the time necessary to fulfill the personal data’s original purpose. Your contact details, access data and analytics cookies are kept indefinitely unless you specifically request for their removal. In the event of a removal request, we will only retain the portion of personal data we believe is needed to comply with the law or other regulatory request. 

* **Data we collect**

We collect information about you in two ways: directly from your inputs and through automated technologies. When you visit our website, your device’s data is automatically logged. This “access data” may include the following information: your device’s IP address; your web browser type/version; your operating system (OS); your internet service provider (ISP); dates/times you accessed the website; websites visited by you prior to accessing our website; and websites you accessed from our website.

We use Google Analytics to collect non-personal information about you. Google Analytics creates a usage profile for each visitor who accesses our website in order to optimize the website’s user experience. A usage profile assigns you with a pseudonym that analyzes your behavior while on the website.  These data are anonymized and are not typically merged with your other Google, Inc. data. For more information on Google Analytics, please visit Google’s privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>. You can object to the use of Google Analytics by changing your browser settings or by following the instructions at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

Our website also collects personal data you voluntarily submit when using features on our website, such as search queries, chat boxes, job applications, information requests, general communications, billing forms, and click data. The personal data we collect may include your contact information (first and last name, email address, mailing address, country of origin, phone number), financial information and any other information you choose to disclose.

* **Special Categories of personal data (sensitive data)**

We do not collect sensitive data (data pertaining to your race, religious or political affiliation, sexual life or orientation) and discourage you from sharing any sensitive data with us or through our website.  We will have no liability whatsoever for sensitive data and this Privacy Policy does not apply to our processing of sensitive data.

* **Cookies we use (Cookie Policy)**

We use cookies to remember your preferences and compile statistics about your activity.  Cookies are small text files that are saved to your device when visiting a website. Certain cookies are deleted when you log out or end the browser session (“transient cookies” or “session cookies”). Other cookies are saved for a specific period of time (“temporary cookies”) or indefinitely (“persistent cookies”). You can learn more about cookies and how to block cookies [here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or on your browser’s support page ([Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies); [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Cookies); [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en); [Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac)).

In general, our use of cookies is limited to remembering that you visited our website and the choices you made while using on the website, such as the length of your web session and the location from which you access the website. 

The following cookies must remain active in order to use the full extent of the Services:

  * cookies that are used to identify or authenticate the user;
  * cookies used to temporarily store user input (e.g. the content of a shopping cart or online form);
  * cookies used to temporarily store marketing campaign information;
  * cookies used to store user preferences (e.g. selection of installation, search or language settings);
  * cookies that store data to enable the trouble-free rendering of video or audio content; and
  * analytics cookies used to record the usage behavior of our users and evaluate it in the form of statistics (e.g. advertising banners clicked, sub-pages visited, search queries conducted).

You may elect to disable cookies on our website, however, choosing to do so may limit some features and your user experience. 

* **How we use your data**

We use your personal data for general marketing and business purposes. These may include:

  * activating, administering, maintaining and troubleshooting our services and website
  * processing and fulfilling requests, orders, and other transactions
  * providing technical support
  * sending marketing communications and newsletters 
  * delivering individualized content, responding to questions and requests, identifying usage trends and developing data analysis
  * enhancing the measures we take to protect the security and integrity of your personal data
  * performing market research and providing you with notifications about general updates and new products and services offered by us and our partners 
  * complying with our legal obligations

For marketing communications, you can revoke consent at any time using the “unsubscribe” process at the bottom of those communications.

* **Sharing Your Data**

We will not sell, market, rent, or otherwise distribute your personal data in ways not contemplated by this Privacy Policy.  We may provide your personal information (i) if we are compelled to do so by law; (ii) with our subsidiaries and affiliates; (iii) to receive third party services (data centers, mailing services, and web tracking); or (iv) in the event of a merger or transfer of all business assets. We maintain strict internal policies that limit when and how we disclose personal data to third parties and will use reasonable efforts to ensure that any third party accessing and/or storing your personal data complies with this Privacy Policy. 

* **Third party content**

Our website integrates external services and links from other third-parties (e.g.: facebook, twitter, youtube). By using the features and links of a third-party service provider, your communication data are sent to the third-party service provider website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third-party cookies, web beacons, or other tracking technologies located on third party websites. 

* **Interest-based Advertising**

We partner with ad exchanges, web analytics vendors, social networking platforms and other third parties to advertise on third-party sites. We allow our partners to use cookies, web beacons, pixels, and other like technologies to target advertisements based on your browsing activities. The data collected from our site by our partners only includes your device’s number ID. Please note, however, that our partners may use your device’s number ID to track other personal data collected about you from other sites and/or other devices you may use to target tailored advertising across all of your devices.  You can opt out of interest-based advertising by following the instructions at <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/> or [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) if you are a resident of the European Union. 

* **Profiling and automated decision-making**

We do not use any fully automated decision-making processes for any of the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and we do not profile you based on the personal data we collect.  However, we may implement behavioral tracking in the future, without further notice, to improve user experience. We use in-market segments in reporting to advertisers to show interest in certain sections of our website.  

* **How we respond to Do-Not-Track signals**

Some browsers have a ”do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser ”do not track” signals, but we do provide you the option to opt out of interest-based advertising. Options you select are browser- and device-specific.

* **Children’s personal data**

Our website and services are not intended to be used by or appeal to children under the age of 16.  If we obtain actual knowledge that we collected personal data provided by a child under the age of 16, we will promptly delete it. If you believe we are in possession of personal data provided by a person under the age of 16, please notify us by email or mail.

Certain laws, based on your geographic location, may provide you with rights to access your personal data and limit how we use it.  If required and/or permitted by the laws of your region, you may be entitled to the rights below: 

  * access your personal data
  * correct any inaccuracies in your personal data
  * have your personal data erased
  * restrict our processing of your personal data
  * transfer your personal data to another controller (if commercially feasible)
  * object to a specific purpose we process your data for
  * exclude yourself from automated decision making based solely on profiling and automated processes 
  * withdraw your consent from us to process your personal data
  * contact the data protection authority in your region with regard to our processing of your personal data

If you wish to exercise any of the rights mentioned above, please contact us and we will work with our privacy team to process and respond to your request within a reasonable time. We may decline to process repetitive and/or impractical requests.

* **Contact Us**

If you provided us with personal data, you can manage how we use your personal data by either emailing or mailing us. Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or information practices should be directed to legal@jumpcrew.com, or by regular mail at: 

Attn: Online Privacy Coordinator/Legal  
JumpCrew  
3201 Dickerson Pike  
Nashville, TN  37207

* **Changes to this Policy.**   

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a revised version and updating the “Effective Date” above. The revised version will be effective on the “Effective Date” listed.
